A Guide to the Asian Cultural Council records, Grants, RG 5 FA1403
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Music, 1963-2006; 16; 30.94 Cubic Feet 79 letter document boxes and 1 record storage box
  - Taiwan, 16.21
    - Change, Juie-Wen, 100-00-94029-203.000-1, 1994 (Box 770, Folder 4)
    - Chao, Yi-Wen, 100-00-24045-203.1, 100-00-22147-203.1, 2002 (Box 770, Folder 5)
    - Metropolitan Opera,100-00-26036-203.3, 2006 (Box 770, Folder 6)
  - Thailand, 16.22
    - Moore, Sidney, DF-6896, 1965 (Box 770, Folder 7)
    - National Guild of Community Music Schools, Music Educator, Bangkok Fine Arts Department, B-7445, B-7146, B-7233, B-7363, Zipper, Herbert, DF-74963, 1971-1974 (Box 770, Folder 8)
    - Bangkok Symphony Orchestra Foundation, DD-8789(90)R, 1987 (Box 770, Folder 9)
    - Society for Asian Music, DF-9175, 1991 (Box 770, Folder 10)
    - Triudom, Sampow, DF-8665, DF-86113, DD-8682(R), DD-86114(65), 1986 (Box 771, Folder 1)
    - Wong, Deborah, B-8865(56)R, 1988 (Box 771, Folder 2)
    - Blasdel, Christopher, 517-00-97151-203.1, 1997 (Box 771, Folder 3)
    - Phoasavadi, Pornprapit, 634-00-22115-203.1, 2002 (Box 771, Folder 4)
  - Tibet, 16.23
    - Samdup, Thubten, B-7436, B-7532, B-7538-AIP, 1974-1975 (Box 771, Folder 5)
    - Vandor, Ivan, B-7247, 1972 (Box 771, Folder 6)
    - International Campaign for Tibet, Ngawang Choephet, 702-00-23015-203.2, 2003 (Box 772, Folder 1)
  - Vietnam, 16.24
    - Dinh Thin, DF-8562, 1985 (Box 772, Folder 2)
    - Arana, Miranda, 706-00-95067-1, 1995 (Box 772, Folder 3)
    - Minnesota Composer Forum, DF-9397, 1993 (Box 772, Folder 4)
    - Nguyen, Phong, 706-00-95068-203.000-1, 1995 (Box 772, Folder 5)
    - Le, Chan Ngoc, 706-00-99075-203.1, 1999 (Box 773, Folder 1)
    - Brown, Elizabeth, 100-00-22068-203.1, 2002 (Box 773, Folder 2)
    - Ha, Tran Thu, 100-00-99012-203.2, 1999 (Box 773, Folder 3)
    - Ngiyen, Co, 100-00-22056-203.1, 100-00-21066-203.1, 100-00-20041-203.1, 100-00-99042-203.1, 100-00-97040-203.1, 1997-2002 (Box 773, Folder 4)
    - Vu, Nhat Tan, 100-00-20052-203.1, 2000 (Box 773, Folder 5)
    - Vu, Nhat Tan, 100-00-20052-203.1, 2000 (Box 774, Folder 1)
    - Tran, Thi Kim Ngoc, 634-00-23090-203.1, 100-00-25035-203.3, 2003; 2005 (Box 774, Folder 2)
    - Thanh, To Ngoc, 100-00-21008-203.3, 2001 (Box 774, Folder 3)
    - Thanh Ngo, Van, 100-00-21065-203.1, 2001 (Box 774, Folder 4)
- Painting and Sculpture, 1964-2007; 17; 32.95 Cubic Feet 87 containers
  - Asia, 17.1
    - Fritz Eichenberg Graphic Arts Survey, P and S-Asia, B-6825, DF-6852, 1968 (Box 774, Folder 5)
    - Asian Printmaking Workshops, B-6925, 1969 (Box 775, Folder 1)
    - Eichenberg, Fritz, University of Rhode Island, B-6825, DF-6852, 1968 (Box 775, Folder 2)
    - MoMA, Two Decades of American Painting, Other than Correspondence, B-6408, 1964 (Box 775, Folder 3)
    - Asia Society, Contemporary Asian Arts, DF-9295, 1992 (Box 775, Folder 4)
    - Elliott, Dennis, 706-00-22083-203.1, 2002 (Box 775, Folder 5)
    - The Mattress Factory, 703-00-99104-203.000-1, 1999 (Box 775, Folder 6)
    - Yerba Buena Center for the Arts, 706-00-21102-203.000-1, 2001 (Box 864, Folder 5)
    - The AiR Association Limited, 703-00-25-20-203.1 (Box 775, Folder 7)
    - Asia Art Archive, 703-00-24111-203.1, 2004 (Box 775, Folder 8)
    - International Forum for Intermedia Art, 706-00-24074-203.1, 2004 (Box 776, Folder 1)
    - International Studio and Curatorial Program, 703-00-25124-203.1, 2005 (Box 776, Folder 2)
    - International Studio and Curatorial Program, 703-00-24113-203.1, 2004 (Box 776, Folder 3)
    - International Studio and Curatorial Program, 703-00-24023-203.2, 2004 (Box 776, Folder 4)
    - Lower Manhattan Cultural Council, 706-00-24009-203.2, 2004 (Box 776, Folder 5)
    - The Quiet in the Land, 718-00-25019, 2005 (Box 776, Folder 6)
    - P.S.1 Contemporary Art Center, 703-00-99025-203.2, 1999 (Box 776, Folder 7)
    - Slayton, Joel, 706-00-2525070-203.1, 2005 (Box 776, Folder 8)
    - TransCultural Exchange, 703-00-24114-203.1, 2004 (Box 777, Folder 1-2)
    - Yerba Buena Center for the Arts, 703-00-23032-203.2, 2003 (Box 777, Folder 3)
    - Ko, Aye (aka Tin Swe), 703-00-24103-203.1, 2004 (Box 777, Folder 4)
    - International Studio and Curatorial Program, 703-00-23030-203.2, 2003 (Box 777, Folder 5)
  - Afghanistan, 17.2
    - Haiderzad, Amanullah, B-7026, EC-7111, 1970-1971 (Box 777, Folder 6)
    - Mikail, Mohammed, DF-7592, DF-7675, B-7703, B-7802, B-7903, 1975-1979 (Box 778, Folder 1)
    - Haiderzad, Amanullah, DF-8101, 1981 (Box 778, Folder 2)
  - China, 17.3
    - [Taiwan] Chuang, Che, B-6651, DF-6804, 1968 (Box 778, Folder 3)
    - Cleveland Museum of Art, DF-6913, 1968 October 11-12 (Box 778, Folder 4)
    - [Taiwan] Yang, Jay, University of Pennsylvania, B-6979, 1969 (Box 778, Folder 5)
    - Yuan, Yun-Sheng, R-8229(20), 1982 (Box 778, Folder 6)
    - Yuan, Yun-sheng, R-8229(20), 1982 (Box 944, Folder 4)
    - Fan, Zhongming, B-8976(27), 1989 (Box 779, Folder 1)
    - Maryland Institute, College of Art, B-9391(27), 1993 (Box 779, Folder 2)
    - Art Omi, Wang Mai, 703-00-21132-203.1, 2001 (Box 779, Folder 3)
    - Art Omi, Jiali Feng, 703-00-21020-203.1, 2001 (Box 779, Folder 4)
    - Art Omi, 703-00-98105-203.1, 1998 (Box 779, Folder 5)
    - California College of Arts and Crafts, 702-00-21026-203.2, 2001 (Box 779, Folder 6)
    - Thomasos, Denyse, 100-00-22066-203.1, 2002 (Box 780, Folder 1)
    - Snug Harbor Cultural Center, 645-00-21150-203.4, 2001 (Box 780, Folder 2)
    - Art-OMI, 703-00-97109-203.000-1, 1997 (Box 780, Folder 3)
    - Borycevica, Mathieu, 100-00-22065-203.1, 2002 (Box 780, Folder 4)
    - Guagdong Museum of Art, 706-00-22091-203.1, 2002 (Box 780, Folder 5)
    - Ho, Heather, 100-00-23120-203.3, 2003 (Box 780, Folder 6)
    - [Taiwan] Chuang, Che, Other than Correspondence, B-6651, 1966; 1968 (Box 781, Folder 1)
    - Humphrey, Nene, 706-00-23064-203.1, 2003 (Box 781, Folder 2)
    - Hung, Keung, 004-00-25061-203.1, 2005 (Box 781, Folder 3)
    - Jiao, Xiaojian, 506-00-20008-203.4, 566-00-99035-203.1, 1999-2000 (Box 782, Folder 1)
    - Lu, Bin, 703-00-21125-203.000-1, 2001 (Box 782, Folder 2)
    - Mao, Xu Hui, 703-00-20116-203.1, 2000 (Box 782, Folder 3)
    - Shanghai Art Museum, 706-00-22093-203.1, 2002 (Box 782, Folder 4)
    - Spalding, David, 706-00-25071-203.1, 2005 (Box 783, Folder 1)
    - Xu Tan, 703-00-22028-203.2, 703-00-21126-203.1, 2001 (Box 783, Folder 2)
    - Xiuzhen Yin and Dong Song, 703-00-26106-203.1, 703-00-25111-203.1, 2006 (Box 783, Folder 3)
    - Wang, Jianwei, 703-00-22121-203.1, 2002 (Box 784, Folder 1)
    - Wang, Qingsong, 703-00-23103-203.1, 2003 (Box 784, Folder 2-3)
    - Wei, Ligang, 735-00-25060-203.1, 2005 (Box 785, Folder 1)
    - Zhang, Jian-jun, B-8776(29)R, 1987 (Box 785, Folder 2-3)
    - [Taiwan] Liu, Kuo-Sung (Mr.), B-6612, B-6723 (Box 950)
  - Hong Kong, 17.4
    - Hon, ChiFun, B-6926, 1969 (Box 785, Folder 4)
    - Wong, Wucius, B-7101, 1971 (Box 786, Folder 1-2)
    - Chu, Hing Wah, B-9353(HK), 1993 (Box 786, Folder 3)
    - Ho, Oscar Hing-Kay, B-9260(HK), 1992 (Box 786, Folder 4)
    - Lau, Kin Wai, B-8777(27)R, 1987 (Box 787, Folder 1)
    - Lai, Victor, B-9164(27), 1991 (Box 787, Folder 2)
    - Man, Phoebe Ching-Ying, 567-00-98062-203.1, 1998 (Box 787, Folder 3)
    - Para-Site Art Space, 100-00-21147-203.3, 2001 (Box 787, Folder 4)
    - Pun, Sydney, B-9358(HK), 1993 (Box 787, Folder 5)
    - Wan, Annie Lai Keun, 100-00-20043-203.2, 599-00-20044-203.1, 2000 (Box 787, Folder 6)
    - Wong, Fiona Lai Ching, 703-00-98101-203.1, 1998 (Box 788, Folder 1)
    - Asia Art Archive, 703-00-23111-203.1, 2003 (Box 788, Folder 2)
    - Asian American Arts Centre, 100-00-25024-203.3, 2005 (Box 788, Folder 3)
    - Choi, Yan Chi, B-8950(HK), 1989 (Box 788, Folder 4)
    - Ho, Siu-Kee, 703-00-20117-203.1, 2000 (Box 789, Folder 1-2)
    - Hong Kong Arts Centre, 100-00-22069-203.1, 2002 (Box 789, Folder 3)
    - So, Yan Kei, 631-00-21090-203.1, 2001 (Box 789, Folder 4)
    - Wong, Shun Kit, 703-00-99101-203.1, 1999 (Box 789, Folder 5)
    - Wong, Shun Kit, 703-00-99101-203.1, 1999 (Box 790, Folder 1-2)
  - India, 17.5
    - Bal Bhavan Children's Art Centre, (MOMA), Painting-Sculpture-India, Other than Correspondence, B-6409, 1964 (Box 790, Folder 3)
    - Bal Bhavan Children's Art Centre (MoMA), B-6409, 1964 (Box 790, Folder 4)
    - Bhatt, Jyoti, DF-6544, B-6608, 1965; 1966 (Box 790, Folder 5)
    - Bhavsar, Natvar, B-6533, 1965 (Box 790, Folder 6)
    - Bose, Arun, B-6929, 1969 (Box 790, Folder 7)
    - Chhabda, Balkrishna L., B-7244, DF-7387, 1973-1974 (Box 791, Folder 1)
    - Chandra, Avinash (Box 791, Folder 2)
    - Davierwalla, A. M., Instittute of International Education (IIE), B-6812, 1968 (Box 791, Folder 3)
    - Gaitonde, Vasudeo, B-6504, 1965 (Box 791, Folder 4)
    - Mehta, Tyeb, B-6813, Pratt, DF-6917, 1969 (Box 791, Folder 5)
    - Padamsee, Akbar, B-6530, 1965 (Box 791, Folder 6)
    - Reddy, Krishna, Printmaking Workshop in New Delhi, B-7357, 1973 (Box 791, Folder 7)
    - Raval, Pallavi V., Skowhegan School, B-7497, 1974 (Box 791, Folder 8)
    - Subramanyan, K. G., B-6655, DF-6792, 1966-1967 (Box 791, Folder 9)
    - Parimoo, Ratan, B-7413, 1974 (Box 792, Folder 1-2)
    - Regional Institute of Printing Technology, B-7345-AIP, B-7538-AIP, 1973; 1975 (Box 792, Folder 3)
    - Khakhar, Bhupen, B-8591(27)R, 1985 (Box 792, Folder 4)
    - Asian Individual, Khakhar, Bhupen P., Vrishchik Publication (Box 792, Folder 5)
    - Kumar, Ram V., B-7032, DF-7181, 1970-1971 (Box 793, Folder 1)
    - Sen, Paritosh, B-7034, 1970 (Box 793, Folder 2)
    - Rodwottiya, Rekah, B-8977(27), 1989 (Box 793, Folder 3)
    - Dave, Vinod, R-8317(27), B-8421, 1983-1984 (Box 794, Folder 1)
    - University of Michigan Museum of Art, Nilima Sheikh, 703-00-23112-203.1, 2003 (Box 794, Folder 2)
  - Indonesia, 17.6
    - Akademi Deni Rupa, Indonesia, P and S-Indo, B-6988, B7278-AIP, 1969-1972 (Box 794, Folder 3)
    - Akademi Seni Rupa Indonesia (ASRI), B-6988, B-7258-AIP, B-7640-AIP, 1969-1976 (Box 794, Folder 4)
    - Bandung Institute of Technology, School Grants Pirous and Affendy, B-6956, B-7144, 1969; 1971 (Box 794, Folder 5)
    - Bandung Institute of Technology, Travel Grants, B-6956-2, B-7144-2, 1969; 1971 (Box 795, Folder 1)
    - Bandung Institute of Technology, Library Books and Equipment, B-6956-3, 1969 (Box 795, Folder 2)
    - Bandung Institute of Technology, School Grants Pirous and Affendy, B-6956, B-7144, 1969; 1971 (Box 795, Folder 3)
    - Dewan Kesenian Djakarta, Arts Council of Djakarta, Painting Equipment, B-6989, DF-7096, B-70103, 1969-1970 (Box 796, Folder 1)
    - Institut Keguruan Dan ILMU Pendidikan (IKIP), Material and Equipment, B-6958, 1969 (Box 796, Folder 2)
    - Institut Keguruan Dan ILMU Pendidikan (IKIP), Sumarjadi Fellowship Award, B-6958, B-7258-AIP, 1969; 1972 (Box 796, Folder 3)
    - Institut Keguruan Dan ILMU Pendidikan (IKIP), B-6958, 1969 (Box 796, Folder 4)
    - Soedarso, A.S.R.I, Travel, B-7416, 1974 (Box 797, Folder 1)
    - Kahar, Adrin, IKIP, University of Iowa, B-7045, B-7312, 1973; 1974 (Box 797, Folder 2)
    - Sinaga, Dolorosa, DF-8553, 1985 (Box 797, Folder 3)
    - 18th Street Arts Complex, Popol Tri Wahyudi Residency, 100-00-22004-203.3, 2002 (Box 797, Folder 4)
    - Sumaatmaja, Bunga Jeruk, 703-00-22029-203.2, 703-00-21127-203.1, 2001-2002 (Box 797, Folder 5)
    - Circle Point Foundation (CP Foundation), 703-00-25123-203.1, 2005 (Box 798, Folder 1)
    - Effendy, Rifky, 703-00-23104-203.1, 2003 (Box 798, Folder 2)
    - Clarion Alley Mural Project, 703-00-22127-203.1, 2002 (Box 798, Folder 3)
    - Feisal, Aramaiani, 703-00-20118-203.1, 100-00-20149-203.3, 2000 (Box 799, Folder 1)
    - Irianto, Asmudjo Jono, 615-24126-203.4, 2004 (Box 799, Folder 2)
    - Siregar, Aminudin, 703-0?02118-203.000-1, 2001 (Box 799, Folder 3)
  - Japan, 17.7
    - McShine, Kynaston (JUSAP), B-8461(30)R, 1984 (Box 800, Folder 1)
    - MOMA (New Japanese Painting and Sculpture, P&S-Japan, other than Correspondence, B-6541, 1965 (Box 800, Folder 2)
    - Shinohara, Ushio, B-6935, 1969 (Box 800, Folder 3)
    - Mizumoto, Shuji, Painting-Japan (Box 800, Folder 4)
    - Nakazato, Hitoshi, P and S-Japan, Other than Correspondence, DF-6682, B-6717, 1966-1967 (Box 800, Folder 5)
    - Ihara, Michio, MIT, EC-7120, 1971 (Box 800, Folder 6)
    - Miki, Tomio, B-7134, DF-7196, B-7250, 1971-1972 (Box 800, Folder 7)
    - Nakazato, Hitoshi, DF-6682, B-6717, DF-6691, 1966-1967 (Box 800, Folder 8)
    - Takamatsu, Jiro, B-7251, 1972 (Box 801, Folder 1)
    - Usami, Keiji, B-6984, B-7217, 1969-1972 (Box 801, Folder 2)
    - Yokoo, Tadanori, DF-6808, 1968 (Box 801, Folder 3)
    - Miyawaki, Aiko (Box 944, Folder 5)
    - Miki, Tomio, P and S-Japan, B-7134, B-7250, 1971-1972 (Box 944, Folder 6)
    - Takamatsu, Jiro, P and S-Japan, B-7251, 1972 (Box 801, Folder 4)
    - Tomura, Hiroshi, P and S-Japan, B-7725, 1977 (Box 801, Folder 5)
    - Shinoda, Tazmi, B-8969(251), 1989 (Box 801, Folder 6)
    - Shirai, Mio, N-9378(390), 1993 (Box 802, Folder 1)
    - Suzuki, Junko, B-8970(251), 1989 (Box 802, Folder 2)
    - Taho, Ritsuko, B-8588(30)R, 1985 (Box 802, Folder 3)
    - Tomura, Hiroshi, B-7725, 1977 (Box 803, Folder 1)
    - Quarterly Review of Design (See Tomura, Hiroshi, B-7725), 1976 Winter (Box 803, Folder 2)
    - Triangle Artsits? Workshop, B-9387(30), 1993 (Box 803, Folder 3)
    - Tsuda, Yoshinori, B-9379(30), 1993 (Box 803, Folder 4)
    - Yanagi, Yukinori, B-9276(330), 1992 (Box 803, Folder 5)
    - Yanagi, Yukinori, B-9276(330), 1992-1994 (Box 804, Folder 1)
    - Usami, Keiji, P and S-Japan, B-6984, 1969 (Box 804, Folder 2)
    - Borofsky, Jonathan, B-8577(30)R, 1985 (Box 804, Folder 3)
    - Lee, U Fan, EC-8333, 1983 (Box 804, Folder 4)
    - Boothe, Power, B-8532(30)R, 1985 (Box 804, Folder 5)
    - Yano, B-8762(30)R, 1987 (Box 805, Folder 1)
    - Graham, Gloria, B-8697(30)R, 1986 (Box 805, Folder 2)
    - ARC-En-Ciel Foundation, EC-9011, 1990 (Box 805, Folder 3)
    - Hafzi, Dimitri (JUSAP), B-7459(30)R, 1974 (Box 805, Folder 4)
    - Hashimoto, Yasuhiko, DD-9004(266), 1990 (Box 805, Folder 5)
    - Hirabayashi, Kaoru, B-8756(30)R, 1987 (Box 805, Folder 6)
    - Itoh, Jinichi, DD-9005(266), 1990 (Box 805, Folder 7)
    - Kawashima, Kiyoshi, B-8757(30)R, 1987 (Box 806, Folder 1-2)
    - Maryland Institute, College of Art, DD-9092 (266) (Box 806, Folder 3)
    - Macaulay, Thomas S., EC-8714(30)R, 1987 (Box 806, Folder 4)
    - Marioni, Tom, B-8535(30)R, 1985 (Box 806, Folder 5)
    - Yasuda, Naoko, B-8967(30), 1989 (Box 807, Folder 1)
    - Arcus Project, Teresita Fernandez, 517-00-97121-203.000-2, 1997 (Box 807, Folder 2)
    - Atlantic Center for the Arts, 704-00-95009-203.000-2, 1995 (Box 807, Folder 3)
    - Gerber, Ava, 479-00-95111-203.000-2, 1995 (Box 807, Folder 4)
    - Ito, Makoto, DF-93105, 1993 (Box 807, Folder 5)
    - Kawamata, Tadashi, B-8433(30)R, 1984 (Box 808, Folder 1-2)
    - Kunimatsu, Asuka, B-9376(390), 1993 (Box 808, Folder 3)
    - Lockhart, Sharon, 494-00-96101-203.000-2, 1996 (Box 808, Folder 4)
    - The Mattress Factory, 704-00-96090-203.000-1, 1996 (Box 809, Folder 1)
    - Matsuo, Megumi, 704-00-94068-203.000-1, 338-00-94069-203.000-1, 1994 (Box 809, Folder 2)
    - Mishima, Kimiyo, B-8656(30)R, 1986 (Box 809, Folder 3)
    - Naito, Rei, B-9272(30), 1992 (Box 809, Folder 4)
    - Ozawa, Tsuyoshi, 488-00-96074-203.000-1, 704-00-96075-203.000-1, 1996 (Box 809, Folder 5)
    - Ogawa, Yuriko, B-8869(30)R, 1988 (Box 810, Folder 1)
    - Sakurai, Chiaki, B-9066(30), 1990 (Box 810, Folder 2)
    - Senzaki, Chieo, B-8870(30)R, 1988 (Box 810, Folder 3)
    - Shiihara, Tomatsu, B-8759(30)R, 1987 (Box 810, Folder 4)
    - Yamaguchi, Keisuke, B-9145(251), 1991 (Box 810, Folder 5)
    - Yoda, Kunio, 488-00-96078-203.000-1, 1996 (Box 811, Folder 1)
    - Addison Gallery of American Art, 100-00-21152-203.3, 2001 (Box 811, Folder 2)
    - Arcus, Justine Kurland, Brad Brown, 704-00-20104-203.1, 2000 (Box 811, Folder 3)
    - Arcus, Douglas Ross, 704-00-22104-203.1, 2002 (Box 811, Folder 4)
    - Bramwell, Michael, 704-00-96080-203.000-1, 1996 (Box 811, Folder 5)
    - Broughel, Barbara, 488-00-96081-203.000-1, 1996 (Box 811, Folder 6)
    - Broughel, Barbara, 479-00-95040-203.000-1, Canceled, 1995 September 15 (Box 811, Folder 7)
    - Carving Studio, 704-00-99021-203.2, 1999 (Box 811, Folder 8)
    - Cheang, Chu Lea, 704-00-20098-203.1, 2000 (Box 811, Folder 9)
    - Coyne, Petah, B-90104(30), 1990 (Box 812, Folder 1-2)
    - Drew, Leonardo, 704-00-97091-203.000-1, 1997 (Box 812, Folder 3)
    - 18th Street Arts Complex, 710-00-98096-203.1, 1998 (Box 812, Folder 4)
    - 18th Street Arts Complex, 710-00-99096-203.000-1, 1999 (Box 812, Folder 5)
    - 18th Street Arts Complex, Inagaki, 100-00-21043-203.3, 704-00-20106-203.1, 2000-2001 (Box 813, Folder 1)
    - Fukuoka Asian Art Museum, 704-00-22022-203.2, 2002 (Box 813, Folder 2)
    - Hirano, Chieko, 572-00-98123-203.4, 1998 (Box 813, Folder 3)
    - Ichi Ikeda, B-8866(30)R, 1988 (Box 813, Folder 4)
    - Ichi Ikeda, B-8866(30)R, 1988 (Box 814, Folder 1)
    - Isozaki, Michiyoshi, 704-00-2110203.1, 2001 (Box 814, Folder 2)
    - Kasahara, Emiko, B-9062(30), 1990 (Box 814, Folder 3)
    - Kaneko, Yuki, 710-00-97097-203.000-1, 1997 (Box 815, Folder 1)
    - Katayama, Mashito, B-8797(30)R, 1987 (Box 815, Folder 2)
    - Kuo, Nina, 704-00-22101-203.1, 2002 (Box 815, Folder 3)
    - Kurachi, Kumiko, 710-00-98095-203.1, 1998 (Box 815, Folder 4)
    - Mattress Factory, 704-00-20108-203.1, 2000 (Box 815, Folder 5)
    - Miyajima, Tatsuo, B-89113(30), 1989 (Box 816, Folder 1)
    - Kaihatsu, Yoshiaki, 100-00-99126-203.3, 710-00-98094-203.1, 1999 (Box 816, Folder 2-3)
    - Muari, Hironori, 704-00-99080-203.000-1, 1999 (Box 817, Folder 1)
    - Motamiya, Kaoru, 100-00-21012-203.3, 710-00-20112-203.1, 2001 (Box 817, Folder 2-3)
    - Nakayama, Daisuke, 710-00-98021-203.2, 710-00-96122-203.1, 1998 (Box 817, Folder 4)
    - Narumi, Nobuhira, B-9273(330), 1992 (Box 818, Folder 1)
    - Nishiyama, Minako, 500-00-97088-203.000-1, 1997 (Box 818, Folder 2)
    - Okada, Hiroko, 704-00-99081-203.000-1, 1999 (Box 818, Folder 3)
    - Organizing Committee for the Yokohama Triennale, 704-00-21120-203.1, 2001 (Box 818, Folder 4)
    - Rodriguez, Geno, 704-00-96083-203.000-1, 1996 (Box 818, Folder 5)
    - Saiki, Katsuhiro, 704-00-22096-203.1, 2002 (Box 819, Folder 1)
    - Shimada, Yoshiko, 704-00-98081-203.1, 1998 (Box 819, Folder 2)
    - Suzuki, Takahiko, 628-00-22099-203.1, 709-00-22151-203.1, 2002 (Box 819, Folder 3)
    - Teipen, Jeremiah, 704-00-21111-203.1, 2001 (Box 819, Folder 4)
    - Taniguchi, Maki, 471-00-95075-203.000-1, 1995 (Box 820, Folder 1)
    - Toride Art Project, 704-00-21119-203.1, 2001 (Box 820, Folder 2)
    - Torimitsu, Momoyo, 100-00-97027-3, 704-00-96077-1, 1997 (Box 820, Folder 3)
    - Ushijima, Tatsumi, 338-00-97072-203.000-1, 1997 (Box 820, Folder 4)
    - Wang, Xinping, 100-00-97137-203.3, 704-00-97090-203.1, 1997 (Box 821, Folder 1-2)
    - Yanaide, Jun?ya, 586-00-20096-203.1, 704-00-20098-203.1, 2000 (Box 821, Folder 3)
    - Yamamoto, Lynne, 704-00-99089-203.000-1, 1999 (Box 821, Folder 4)
    - Yoshida, Gyoko, 710-00-21122-203.1, 2001 (Box 822, Folder 1)
    - Yomogizawa, Shoko, 338-00-94073-203.000-1, 1994 (Box 822, Folder 2)
    - Abe, Aachiko, 710-00-23073-203.1, 704-23074-203.1, 2003 (Box 822, Folder 3)
    - Aida, Makoto, 710-00-99095-203.1, 1999 (Box 822, Folder 4)
    - ARCUS, Santiago Cucullu, 704-00-24086-203.1, 2004 (Box 823, Folder 1)
    - ARCUS, Sanford Biggers, 704-00-23083-203.1, 2003 (Box 823, Folder 2)
    - ARCUS, Kristin Lucas, 100-00-99054-203.1, 1999 (Box 823, Folder 3)
    - ARCUS, James Sheehan and Erick Cheng Tsai Chen, 704-00-21115-203.1, 2001 (Box 823, Folder 4)
    - ARCUS Project, Jeannie Crosby, 517-00-98074-203.1, 1998 (Box 823, Folder 5)
    - Barac, Jan, 704-00-23078-203.1, 2003 (Box 823, Folder 6)
    - Crocetta, Alison, 704-00-25086-203.1, 2005 (Box 823, Folder 7)
    - Cai, Guo Qiang, 471-00-95070-203.000-1, 1995 (Box 823, Folder 8)
    - Cai, Guo Qiang, 471-95070-1, 1995 (Box 824, Folder 1-2)
    - California Institute of the Arts, 704-00-24087-203.1, 2004 (Box 824, Folder 3)
    - Clark Center for Japanese Art, 100-00-98118-203.3, 1998 (Box 824, Folder 4)
    - Furukawa, Chisen, B-9160(308), 1991 (Box 824, Folder 5)
    - Furukawa, Chisen, B-9160(308), 1991 (Box 825, Folder 1)
    - Grey Art Gallery, 704-00-27088-203.1, 2007 (Box 825, Folder 2)
    - Furukawa, Yumiko, 710-00-24076-203.1, 704-00-24077-203.1, 2004 (Box 825, Folder 3)
    - Hasegawa, Yuko, 100-00-25002-203.3, 2005 (Box 825, Folder 4)
    - Kanai, Yoshiko, B-9375(390), B-9374(30), DF-93111, 1993 (Box 634, Folder 2)
    - Kimura, Yuki, 710-00-22109-203.1, 2002 (Box 825, Folder 5)
    - McCoy, Karen, 704-00-26087-203.1, 2006 (Box 826, Folder 1-2)
    - Murakami, Takashi, 338-00-94070-203.000-1, 1994 (Box 826, Folder 3-4)
    - Moriyama, Tomoe, 732-00-25090-203.1, 2005 (Box 826, Folder 5)
    - Nawa, Kohei, 686-00-24079-203.1, 2004 (Box 827, Folder 1)
    - Nishjima, Atsushi, 704-00-21106-203.1, 2001 (Box 827, Folder 2)
    - Oiwa, Oscar Saito, 605-00-21107-203.000-1, 2001 (Box 827, Folder 3)
    - Oiwa, Oscar Saito, 605-00-21107-203.000-1, 2001 (Box 828, Folder 1)
    - Okazaki, Kenjiro, B-8587(30)R, 1985 (Box 828, Folder 2-3)
    - Okazaki, Kenjiro, B-8587(30)R, 1985 (Box 829, Folder 1)
    - Okumura, Yuki, 686-00-25082-203.1, 2005 (Box 829, Folder 2)
    - Sakuma, Toshihiro, B-9275(330), 1992 (Box 829, Folder 3)
    - Sakuma, Toshihiro, B-9275(330), 1992 (Box 830, Folder 1)
    - Skowhegan School of Painting and Sculpture, 704-00-25098-203.1, 2005 (Box 830, Folder 2)
    - Tanaguchi, Gaho, 704-00-24010-203.2, 2004 (Box 830, Folder 3)
    - Tanaguchi, Gaho, 100-00-96104-203.000-3, 471-00-95074-203.1, 1996 (Box 830, Folder 4)
    - Tanaka, Koki, 704-00-24080-203.1, 648-00-23076-203.1, 2004 (Box 830, Folder 5)
    - Tanaka, Koki, 704-00-24080-203.1, 648-00-23076-203.1, 2004 (Box 831, Folder 1)
    - Tazoe, Kaori, 748-00-26081-203.1, 2006 (Box 831, Folder 2)
    - Wynter, Christopher, 704-00-21114-203.1, 2001 (Box 831, Folder 3)
    - Yokono, Kenichi, 710-00-25085-203.1, 2005 (Box 831, Folder 4-5)
    - Ozutsumi, Ryoichi (Mr.), DD-9003(266), 1990 (Box 941, Folder 5)
    - Yanagimoto, Isao (Mr.), DD-9006(266), 1990 (Box 941, Folder 6)
  - Korea, 17.8
    - Kim, Whanki (Box 832, Folder 1)
    - Choi, Man Lin, B-7521, 1975 (Box 832, Folder 2)
    - Kim, Byung-ki, DF-6603, 1966 (Box 832, Folder 3)
    - Kim, Tschang-Yeul, DF-6604, B-6939, DF-7081, 1966-1970 (Box 832, Folder 4)
    - Kim, Whanki, B-6502, DF-6431, DF-6551, DF-6606, DF-6642, 1964-1966 (Box 832, Folder 5)
    - Kim, Whanki, B-6502, DF-6431, DF-6551, Other than Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 832, Folder 6)
    - Kim, Woong, B-7820, 1978 (Box 833, Folder 1)
    - Park, Chong Bae, Cranbrook Academy, B-6819, 1968 (Box 833, Folder 2)
    - Youn, Myeung-Ro, B-6941, 1969 (Box 833, Folder 3)
    - Choi, Man-Lin, College of Fine Arts, Seoul National University, B-7521, 1975 (Box 833, Folder 4)
    - Youn, Myeung To, B-6941, 1969 (Box 833, Folder 5)
    - 18th Street Arts Complex, 703-00-24112-203.1, 2004 (Box 833, Folder 6)
    - Ha, Yong-Sox, 703-00-96093-203.000-1, 1996 (Box 833, Folder 7)
    - Nam, Kiho, 638-00-21146-203.4, 2001 (Box 834, Folder 1-2)
    - Shin, Jean, 100-00-21072-203.1, 2001 (Box 834, Folder 3)
    - Cho, Min, B-9078(27), 1990 (Box 834, Folder 4-5)
    - Lee, Jeongkyu, R-8318(27), 1983 (Box 835, Folder 1)
  - Malaysia, 17.9
    - Khoo, Sui Hoe, Related Material (Box 835, Folder 2)
    - Sui-Ho Khoo, B-7442, 1974 (Box 835, Folder 3)
    - Lim Eng Hooi, B-7824, B-7883, 1978 (Box 835, Folder 4)
    - Hussein, Ibrahim, Institute of International Education (IIE), B-6773, DF-69107, 1967; 1969 (Box 835, Folder 5)
    - Latiff, Abdul, B-6942, 1969 (Box 836, Folder 1)